Tlingit songs and texts collected by Nora Marks Dauenhauer and Richard Dauenhauer
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Tlingit and English recordings, ca. 1950-1997 Bulk: 1970-1990
  - Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 12, 1978, Tape 304.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR203)
    Speaker's English name: Walter (Babe) Williams; George Davis; Eva Davis; Forrest Dewitt. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Talking about food, money, and life, and storing artifacts in an archive. They talk about living away from their heritage. They also talk about diseases and medicing, modern and Tlingit, as well as hunting and foraging.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 12, 1978, Tape 305.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR204)
    Speaker's English name: Walter (Babe) Williams; unknown. Speaker's Tlingit Name: Keidlak'i Éesh. Speaker's Moiety: Ch'áak' (Eagle). Speaker's Crest: Xóots (Brown Bear). Speaker's Clan: Chookaneidí (Hoonah). Father's Clan: unknown. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Fireweed roots, Devil's Club roots, Elderberry roots, more on Tlingit style medicine. Discussion about who record, how to record, and where to store these collections. Short memorial for Henry Bremner.
  - George Davis, Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 12, 1978, Tape 306.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR205)
    Speaker's English name: George Davis. Speaker's Tlingit Name: Kichnáalx; Lk'aanáaw. Speaker's Moiety: Ts'axweil (Crow) *Raven. Speaker's Crest: S'igeidí (Beaver). Speaker's Clan: Deisheetaan (Angoon). Father's Clan: Kaagwaantaan yádi. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference; George presses to split the group because he fears he will take too long with all the information he knows and he wants to let others talk. Discussion of Tlingit names of months. Recording continues in a restaurant until the end. They talk about the Sitka battle and how the Sitka Russians left.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 12, 1978, Tape 307.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR206)
    Speaker's English name: William Nelson; Eva Davis; George Davis; Walter (Babe) Williams; Forrest Dewitt; President of Sitka IRA. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer; unknown. Description of contents: Comforting William Nelson, as he lost a family member during the Conference. Discussing where and how to store recordings and history of Alaska Natives. Explanation of what harvest is available during which months. Also telling about medicine in the wilderness. Mk02200 recording volume is poor. Inaudible until end.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 13, 1978, Tape 308.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR207)
    Speaker's English name: Vesta Johnson; Walter (Babe) Williams; George Davis; Charlie Joseph; Austin Hammond. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer; unknown. Description of contents: Tlingit prayers from the Bible and Tlingit Beliefs. Raven story, history before the Flood, coming of the Russians and trading of molasses, rice, and liquor. George tells about subsistence living. Working for Tlingit and Haida wage differences.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearers' Conference, April 13, 1978, Tape 309.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR208)
    Speaker's English name: George Davis; Walter (Babe) Williams; Charlie Joseph; Austin Hammond; Dick Hotch; George James. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer; unknown. Description of contents: Oratory on tradition. Group discussion with three speakers on traditional subjects such as subsistence, healing, land, and language. Continuation: Austin Hammond speaks at the beginning, followed by Dick Hotch, Charlie Joseph and George James. Closing remarks by Walter Babe Williams.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearersʼ Conference: Seminar, April 13, 1978, Tape 310.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR209)
    Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: unknown.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearersʼ Conference: Seminar, April 14, 1978, Tape 311.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR210)
    Speaker's English name: Walter (Babe) Williams; Ellen Hays; George Davis. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Introduction by Walter Babe Williams. Ellen Hays speaks in English about the National Park center, and significance of cultural history in Sitka. George Davis translates for Ellen after she speaks and describes traditional methods of healing, traditional practices, and the significance of recorded cultural history. Closing comments by Walter Babe Williams.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearersʼ Conference: Seminar, April 12, 1978, Tape 312.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR211)
    Speaker's English name: Eva Davis; George Davis; Forrest Dewitt; William Nelson; Nora Dauenhauer. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Side A: Recording starts with Nora Dauenhauer interviewing or recording with Eva Davis. Speaker changes at 10:21, probably to George Davis and to a somewhat informal discussion. Forrest Dewitt speaks briefly at one point. There is more than one conversation going on at a couple of points until about 24:00. Break at 30:19. Side B: Recording begins with a speaker, no introduction. The speaker tells of drinking water from a cup, and a Christian cross forms in the bottom of his cup. He finishes drinking from the cup and has a spiritual experience (speaking in tongues, Russian). He tells of another encounter, hunting with his nephew. They are attacked by a bear, who is finally killled by the speaker with a knife. He finishes his speech with explaining how his experiences have helped him to realize becoming a shaman.
  - Sitka Tradition Bearersʼ Conference: Seminar, April 14, 1978, Tape 313.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR212)
    Speaker's English name: Eva Davis; George Davis; Forrest Dewitt; Walter Babe Williams; Nora Dauenhauer. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Sitka, Alaska. Recorded by: Nora Marks Dauenhauer. Description of contents: Side A: Recording begins with Forrest Dewitt, no introduction. He speaks about the Juneau area and landmarks, ends at 31:00. George Davis speaks briefly, and posts are elected: chair, vice chair, and secretary. Side B: Recording with dialogue, 1 song. The dialogue is between Nora, Johnny and Willie Marks, though Willie is inaudible.
  - Recording Session on Tlingit Song, June 6, 1980, Tape 314.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR213)
    Speaker's English name: Johnny Marks; George Dalton. Speaker's Tlingit Name: unknown; Stoowukáa. Speaker's Moiety: Yéil (Raven); Ch'áak' (Eagle). Speaker's Crest: Sockeye; unknown. Speaker's Clan: Lukaax.ádi (Haines); Kaagwaantaan (Hoonah). Father's Clan: Chookaneidí yádi; T'akdeintaan yádi. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Angoon, Alaska. Recorded by: unknown. Description of contents: Recording with dialogue in Tlingit and English, with songs. Many speakers; only George and Jessie Dalton are recognizable.
  - George Dalton Party, Angoon, June 6, 1980, Tape 315.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR214)
    Speaker's English name: Jessie Dalton; George Dalton; George Jim; unknown speakers. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Angoon, Alaska. Recorded by: unknown. Description of contents: Traditional style of speaking, ceremonial. A ceremonial staff or long cane may have been presented/brought out. The dialogue reflects the manner of speech when such an item is brought out as a matter of protocol. Ceremonial, bringing out of money, giving names. Context of the party is still unknown. Recording may be from the collection of Al Kookesh.
  - George Dalton Party, Angoon, June 6, 1980, Tape 316.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR215)
    Speaker's English name: George Jim; George Dalton; unknown speakers. Language: Tlingit/English. Location recorded: Angoon, Alaska. Recorded by: unknown. Description of contents: Closing remarks. Several speakers (unknown) speaking in turn. Audio quality diminishes at about 24:30, dialogue and speaker identity are not identifiable. Wax cylinder recordings of songs, ca 1904. Asterisk on track 8 denotes that Nora took a special interest in the transcription ("Tlingit Myths and Texts," p. 390-414), and identified the song as a "Boys' Lullaby" from her childhood, as sung by her parents to her brothers.
  - JR Swanton 1904 wax cylinders, 1904, Tape 317.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR216)
    Description of contents: Date reflects when tape copy was made. Copy of J. R. Swanton 1904 wax cylinders. #7211.
  - [Frederica] De Laguna LWO 3859, March 8, 1977, Tape 318.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR217)
    Description of contents: Date reflects when tape copy was made. Side A. De Laguna, LWO 3859. 11,998. Side B. De Laguna, side I of reel I, LWO 3858.
  - [Frederica] De Laguna LWO 3859, March 8, 1977, Tape 319.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR218)
    Description of contents: Date reflects when tape copy was made. Side A. 3-8-77, de Laguna LWO 3859, Side II reel I. Side B. side II, reel I, LWO 3859, de Laguna 11,998.
  - [Frederica] De Laguna LWO 3859, March 8, 1977, Tape 320.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR219)
    Description of contents: Date reflects when tape copy was made. Start reel II, LWO 3859, de Laguna. Side B. reel II, side I, LWO 3859, de Laguna.
  - [Frederica] De Laguna LWO 3859, March 8, 1977, Tape 321.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR220)
    Description of contents: Date reflects when tape copy was made. Side 2 of reel 2 de Laguna. Side B. Continued. Side [sic] of reel 2. de Laguna.
  - Emma Marks, Willie Marks, J. B. Fawcett, October 2-4, 1972, Tape 322.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR221)
    Description of contents: Side A. October 2, 1972. Emma Marks, Killer Whale. Side B. October 3, 1972, J. B. Fawcett, October 4, 1972, Willie Marks. From the card insert, side A appears to have 1) Kooshdaa Kaa, 2) Kooshdaa Kaa, 3) Xakuch' (presumably by Willie Marks. Side B, Naatsilanei, T'aaku, Tl'anaxeedakw by J B Fawcett; Naatsilanei by Willie Marks. Has old label tape No. 2. This is probably one of the first tapes made by Nora on her year with ANLC. Probably taped at Marks Trail, Juneau.
  - Willie Marks, October 8, 1974, Tape 323.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR222)
    Description of contents: Juneau.
  - Willie Marks, Juneau, October 26, 1980, Tape 324.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR223)
    Description of contents: Side 1. 1) Auke Bay History, Tl'anaxeedákw. 2) Taxgwás', story from South. Side 2. 1) End of Taxgwás' 2) background of his carving, 3) L'awtáak, 4) Raven and fire 5) Social Security bonus oil money.
  - Willie Marks, October 26, 1980, Tape 325.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR224)
    Description of contents: Side 1, Ch'eetk'. Side 2, unidentified content.
  - Willie, John, Emma, and Nora Marks, January 5, 1974, Tape 326.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR225)
    Description of contents: unidentified content.
  - Emma Marks, undated, Tape 327.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR226)
  - Emma Marks, on Italio River, undated, Tape 328.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR227)
  - Johnny Marks stories, undated, Tape 329.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR228)
    Description of contents: This is taped over an older recording labeled "Dental Meeting, Jan 24-25, 1980. Check the flip side to see if it is John Marks or the dental meeting. If unsure, migrate both sides.
  - Emma and Jenny Marks, Lullabies, August 23, 1972, Tape 330.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR229)
    Description of contents: Older number on label is #58.
  - Jessie Kasko and Jenny Marks at Raven House, undated, Tape 332.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR230)
  - Jenny Marks, Haines, July 6, 1974, Tape 333.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR231)
    Description of contents: Cassette is labeled "Haines III" so this may be the companion to another tape elsewhere in the collection.
  - Jenny Marks, January 14, 1975, Tape 334.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR232)
    Description of contents: Uncle Jim's Gun and Song. Side two is labeled, "meeting of some kind."
  - Jenny Marks, undated, Tape 335.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR233)
    Description of contents: Bear Hat Song.
  - Horace Marks, undated, Tape 336.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR234)
    Description of contents: Label reads: "Introduction. Narrator Horace Marks. Agnes Bellinger Library."
  - Horace Marks and Austin Hammond, August, 1984, Tape 337.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR235)
  - Marks Trail Dancers' songs, ca. 1965-1970, Tape 338.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR236)
    Description of contents: "This is a very old recording probably from the late 1960s, by Rosita Worl on a trip with Nora in conjunction an Alaska State Museum trip to Haines and Klukwan. Has old number #52. Contents: 1) ch'uh adei – Haines, 2) ch'uh adei Juneau, Marks Trail, 3) Go for Broke, Haines, 4) Go for Broke, Juneau."
  - Jimmie Marks, July 2, 1982, Tape 339.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR237)
    Description of contents: "Jimmie Marks, Juneau. Xwaayeenak song, for Nora. July 2, 1982, Anchorage. This is probably a 1982 copy of an earlier recording by Jim Marks (1881-1967)."
  - Chookaneidi cry songs and love songs, undated, Tape 340.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR238)
    Description of contents: "Handwriting unclear—possibly Amy Marvin and Nora. Contents: 1) some songs, 2) yeik—headdress dance, 3) Chookaneidi, chaatl yaakw, 4) Eeshaan gushei, 5) aya x'aaxa, 6) yaakw, 7) Ch'áak' s'áaxw, 8) yaanáx yéi kkwlashaataa, 9) waa sa haa kgwatee, 10) K'astook Eesh."
  - Nora's song, January, 1983, Tape 341.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR239)
  - Johnny Marks and Nora, August 2, 1983, Tape 342.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR240)
  - Robert Zuboff and Susie James, July 27, 1972, Tape 343.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR241)
    Description of contents: Side A. Robert Zuboff. Side B. Robert Zuboff and Susy James.
  - Susy James, July 28, 1972, Tape 344.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR242)
    Description of contents: "Numbering suggests this is tape 3 of that day. Other labeling is "SJ 3."
  - Susy James Workshop, reading of Glacier Bay, June, 1973, Tape 345.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR243)
    Description of contents: "According to the label, this is the Tlingit Language workshop group reading the transcription of Susie James' telling of the Glacier Bay History, recorded by Nora Dauenhauer in June 1972 and published in August 1973. This tape probably dates from June 1973."
  - Susy James, September, 1972, Tape 346.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR244)
    Description of contents: "This is a copy of an original recorded by Mary Pelayo."
  - Susy James, Chookaneidi Songs, May 11, 1973, Tape 347.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR245)
    Description of contents: "Chookaneidi Songs, recorded by Nora Florendo (Dauenhauer), May 11, 1973. Has old number SJ 01."
  - Susy James, May 31, 1973, Tape 348.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR246)
    Description of contents: "Sitka, May 31, 1973. Side 1, Misc. Side 2, Daa k'i keena."
  - Susy James (Kaaxsgeiy), Yuwaan Gageets, undated, Tape 349.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR247)
  - Susy James, undated, Tape 350.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR248)
    Description of contents: 1) Shaawatch Géel', 2) Ch'eet, 3) Kooshdaa taayi kaachkéex, 4) her childhood, Kaachkéex, 5) Tax' Hit taa yatx'i 6) Gaanaaxaa yat'ak Tloon Tlaa du tlaa wutaax'u.
  - George Jim, 1990s, Tape 351.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR249)
    Description of contents: Labeled, "special."
  - John and Emma Marks; David Kadashan, June, August, 1972, Tape 352.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR250)
    Description of contents: John and Emma Marks, June 4, 1972. David Kadashan August 10, 1972. Side 2 has both "blank" and David Kadashan on it.
  - Charlie Jim, undated, Tape 353.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR251)
  - Tom Jimmy, Klukwan, April 27, 1970, Tape 354.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR252)
    Description of contents: "A. Origin of Shangukeidi."
  - A. P. Johnson, ca. 1970, Tape 355.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR253)
    Description of contents: From cassette label: "Thanks for the reader."
  - A. P. Johnson, August 20, 1983, Tape 356.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR254)
    Description of contents: "Sheldon Jackson College, Sitka. Demonstrating traditional Tlingit weapons; English with Tlingit names."
  - Charlie Joseph, Sr, July, 1990, Tape 357.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR255)
    Description of contents: "Bear Song. Recorded by Thomas Thornton, Angoon."
  - Mrs George Karteedee; Mrs J. C. Johnnson, July, 1971, Tape 358.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR256)
    Description of contents: "Side 1. Mrs George Karteedee, Hoonah, July 1971. Side 2. Mrs J. C. Johnnson, Hoonah, July 21, 1971. Recorded by Nora Florendo (Dauenhauer)."
  - Herman Kitka, February 28, 1996, Tape 359.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR257)
    Description of contents: Recorded by Nora Dauenhauer in Juneau at Sealaska Heritage Foundation.
  - Amy Marvin, June 5, 1986, Tape 360.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR258)
    Description of contents: "Amy Marvin, Hoonah, June 5, 1986. Side 1 is labeled "Part of Side 4, side 5. Accompanying cassettes may be elsewhere in the collection."
  - Topsy Martin, Kake, November 21, 1992, Tape 361.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR259)
    Description of contents: "The only ID is 'received from Topsy Martin, Kake, Alaska.'"
  - William Nelson on Eli Katanook, 1980, Tape 362.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR260)
    Description of contents: Recorded by Sergei Kan, summer 1980.
  - Joe Paddock, April 20, 1993, Tape 363.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR261)
    Description of contents: Sitka.
  - Albert Paddy, April 26, 2001, Tape 364.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR262)
    Description of contents: Klukwan.
  - Albert Paddy, April 26, 2001, Tape 365.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR263)
    Description of contents: Klukwan. Cassette 2.
  - Albert Paddy, April 26, 2001, Tape 366.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR264)
    Description of contents: Klukwan. Cassette 3.
  - William L. Paul, Sr., June 22-23, 1970, Tape 367.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR265)
    Description of contents: "Reading his autobiography. Box is dated June 23, cardboard insert to cassette is dated June 22."
  - William L. Paul, Sr., June 24, 1970, Tape 368.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR266)
    Description of contents: "Tlingit culture. Recorded by Nora Florendo (Dauenhauer) and Rosita Rodriguez (Worl). Cassette is labeled 'Tape 1.' Continues on side 2."
  - James Ward; Tom Peters, September 5-6, 1972, Tape 369.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR267)
    Description of contents: "Side A. James Ward, Whitehorse, September 5 or 6, 1972. Side B. Tom Peters, Teslin, September 8, 1972. Tom Peters on visiting between interior and coast, Tukweidi & Deisheetaan, gáax'oo, Deisheeteaan houses. Has old # 13."
  - Lily White, May 16, 1994, Tape 370.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR268)
  - Ernestine Hanlon, February 18, 1991, Tape 371.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR269)
    Description of contents: "Hoonah, February 18, 1991. The poem on p 87 of "Life Woven with Song" probably dates from the time and place of this recording."
  - Jim Young, undated, Tape 373.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR270)
    Description of contents: "Glacier Bay. No date. Note on cassette, 'Possibly 3rd generation of tape.'"
  - Jim Young, undated, Tape 374.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR271)
    Description of contents: "Glacier Bay II. No date. Note on cassette, 'Possibly 3rd generation of tape.'"
  - Lydia George, June 1, 1988, Tape 375.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR272)
    Description of contents: Angoon.
  - Austin Hammond, March, 1998, Tape 376.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR273)
    Description of contents: "Translated by Rachel Johnson. Copy. March 1998. There appears to be an original source number: 91.208.02. This may refer to the Haines radio station file. Dan Henry might know."
  - Johnny C. Jackson, October, 1971, Tape 377.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR274)
    Description of contents: "Kake totem raising, October 1971. Has older #23. This may be the source of the speeches in HTY, 162 ff."
  - Johnny C. Jackson, March 3, 1981, Tape 378.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR275)
    Description of contents: Kake stories.
  - Johnny C. Jackson, March 3, 1981, Tape 379.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR276)
    Description of contents: Kake stories. "(Presumably a second copy and not a copy of Tape 378)."
  - Johnny C. Jackson, August 10, 1983, Tape 380.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR277)
    Description of contents: "Mt Edgecumbe, August 10, 1983. Has old #35. This is probably the companion tape to CD #148 in this archive. The label is almost impossible to read, with by looking at light and shadows, it reads 'Gooch Eesh 8-10-83 Mt Edgecumbe.'"
  - Robert James, Sr., November 23, 1992, Tape 382.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR278)
    Description of contents: "Angoon, November 23, 1992. Speaking about Alex Andrews."
  - Jessy Dalton, June 6, 1986, Tape 383.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR279)
    Description of contents: Hoonah. Picnic.
  - Jessy Dalton, ca. 1972, Tape 384.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR280)
    Description of contents: Mt. Edgecumbe Hospital.
  - Marion Dennis, October 1, 1972, Tape 385.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR281)
  - Jenny Klanott (Thlunaut), October 25, 1973, Tape 386.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR282)
  - Bert Dennis memorial, October 5, 1974, Tape 387.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR283)
    Description of contents: Haines Memorial ANB Hall, Haines, Alaska.
  - J.B. Fawcett, 1969, Tape 388.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR284)